Hey, Aquadine. This is uh Greg here.
Congratulations. Welcome to Tampa. Uh
just just want to ask you what you like
about the Bucks. I'm sure you had
options in free agency. What made you
want to come to the Bucks?
>> Um well, my last uh Dline coach, Casey
Rogers, he was um coaching in Tampa. So,
you know, um me and him spoke and um you
know, he said it would be a great fit
and stuff like that. He said I really I
really like it and stuff. So, you know,
I knew there was some familiarity uh
there. So, you know, I felt really
confident and I felt happy about it,
excited about it.
>> Thank you.
>> We'll go to River Wells.
>> Hey, welcome to Tampa. Um, I wanted to
ask, you've been teammates with Alex
Analone, uh, three on three different
teams. Now, this the third one, Saints,
uh, Liz here.
>> What can you say about him and the type
of player he is and how excited you are
to work with him again here in Tampa
Bay?
>> Wow. Um, well, we was drafted together
um to the Saints in 2017.
He's a great extinctive uh smart
football player. Me and him are really
close, really good friends. So, I'm
super excited to be able to be on a new
team and um you know, still play with
him. So, you know, it's amazing, you
know, um I'm excited about it, you know,
just to just to have somebody that
you've been out there um in games, live
action, you know, with and I just know
what he's about and um you know, he's
always the standard. So, just just
really happy and excited to be out there
with Enzo and to be on a in a new team,
new organization with Enzelone
>> Rick Straoud.
Hey, Aquin. Um, last year, uh, I think
it was 11 sacks, you had a hell of a
year rushing the passer. Uh, just tell
me what was working for you, how how you
improved that area.
>> Um, you know, just, uh,
wow. uh signing off a P squad the first
year around when I was with the Lions
and um you know got an opportunity to
get out there and play after some guys
got injury um injured
>> you know just really just you know
getting back to you know myself and
feeling really extremely healthy and you
know building my body up changed some
things during the off season and um you
know really just locked in and worked on
different things uh pass rush wise and
um got that opportunity had a great gig
come back, you know, um they sign me
back and, you know, wind up having 11
sacks and uh you know, just just playing
playing with a, you know, a great
defense and having some great unique uh
guys around me. And um just each game,
you know, you have a little bit success,
you get more confident, you get more
comfortable,
>> and you know, also, you know, me and
Aiden Hutcherson, we compliment each
other really, really well. So,
>> you know, that also uh plays a part and
you know, just keeping that competitive
a u competitive nature. We just was just
talking about that that you know, when
you know, I'm having success, he having
success, just feeding off each other
and, you know, wanting to create that
battle to get to the quarterback. And uh
I think, you know, that's definitely
something that we're going to do here.
>> And you mentioned Alex, you know, he
plays a certain attitude. You do
certainly. Uh Aan Robinson's coming in
here. It takes a little bit of edge,
right? You got to be a little edgy out
there. A little bit of snarl. So, what
do you make of the of the group that you
guys are assembling here with the Vita
and guys like that that are already
here. Just that that little extra gear
that you guys have when you play. I
>> mean, ultimately, you have to build that
chemistry and you build that over time.
You build that in OTAAS, you build that
in camp. And um you know, you kind of
see how guys do things, how they play,
play style and different stuff like
that. And it's all about just really,
you know, feeding off each other,
jelling together, communicating and
understanding, you know, what we like to
do within the scheme. And um, you know,
just really jelling together and keep
building upon that. You know, we all
have uh different skill sets. That's,
you know, amazing skill sets, but what
what does that look like ultimately when
we go out there and we play, you know,
play together, you know? So um it's
really just just building that team
camaraderie um learning each other
having fun while doing it and everybody
um you know giving maximum effort and
also just talking ball you know how I
see things how uh you know Enzo see
things va see how different guys you
know see different things and ultimately
you know we're ball players and and
we'll figure it out and we make it work
and then also you know co the coaches to
put us in the right positions and that
plays that play a major part too. So,
you know, I have all the confidence in
the world that we going to go out there
and do what we need to do and uh, you
know, have a great season.
>> Jenna,
>> welcome to Tampa. Um, you're coming to a
team that has seldom had a guy in a
single season get double digit sacks.
So, like what does that mean for you to
be able to come to a place where you
could really have the potential to make
an impact like that?
Um, it's amazing. It's amazing, but
ultimately um, you know, it doesn't mean
anything if you don't put the work in.
And, um, you know, it starts from day
one and, you know, we all in offseasons
and we all have our routines and stuff
like that. So it starts ultimately, you
know, with that, you know, doing the
little things, taking care of your body,
training, building that foundation, and
then, you know, going out there and
learning, you know, um how our coaches,
our staff, how my teammates, my new
teammates like to do things and and and
and keep just building, you know, just
building a strong foundation and then
when you get out there on field on the
field in practice and stuff like that,
you just let it rip, you know. So
ultimately, you know, last year was last
year. This is a new season. This is a
new team, new organization, and I'm
looking forward to building on what some
of the stuff that I did do last year,
but um I'm extremely excited and uh it
it feels it feels like it's a it's a
great fit. But ultimately, it's the
little things and and I'm, you know,
building my foundation, building the
things that I need to do to um to have a
better season than than last year. last
year was last year, but ultimately I
always look at, you know, ways to get
better and expand on what was done in
the past.
>> And if I can follow up, um, for that to
happen in year eight for you, um, I know
sometimes guys will overthink things,
you know, and that kind of slows them
down when they're rushing. Um, some guys
they they maybe work on a few moves or
they just have a better feel for how to
attack, you know, offensive tackles. for
you, what what do you think it was that
that just really clicked for you this
past year?
>> Um,
it's really, you know, the longer you
play in this league and the longer you
play in this in in in the NFL, you learn
um a lot of different things and it's
really a chess match. you know, is it a
it's a chess match
and then you figure out, you know, what
some guys with your opponent with the
tackles, what they like to do and how,
you know, they're trying to attack the
defense and and it's really a chess
match, you know, and ultimately, you
know, overthinking don't get you
nowhere. You know, I know you mentioned
some things some some guys tend maybe
you may overthink. Overthinking gets you
nowhere, you know. You just play fast
and you let it rip and you play play the
game within a game. And ultimately, you
know, that's what I learned how to do as
I um, you know, grow and develop, you
know, throughout my career, you know,
just learn how to play the game within
the game and have fun by doing it and
also giving that knowledge to, you know,
um, the other guys in the room. And
that's what it's about, you know, that
way everybody is having success. It's
not about me. It's about all of us
having some fun and having success and
playing together and playing fast and
physical and you know everybody would
definitely you know be happy at the end
of the year. So ultimately that's that's
that's how I see it.
>> We'll go to Scott Reynolds next.
>> Congratulations on coming to Tampa. You
play with a relentless playing style.
Where does that that come from? You're a
very physical nasty football player.
What what's the origin of that for you?
I was a sixth round draft pick. Um pick
196. So ultimately, you know, um you
have to play with that chip on your
shoulder. You have to earn your keep.
Nothing is given to you. And I wouldn't
rather it any other way. So, you know,
um sometimes if you if you make a
mistake or if you lack in other areas,
you know, you can you can um clean those
things up by playing fast and physical.
And al also it's like you know a coach
make a good call great coach make a bad
call you could you could make you could
make up you know you won't even know
it's a bad call or it wasn't the best
position you know maybe a coach put us
in if you're playing balls to the walls
you playing 100 miles per hour if you're
playing relentless you know it it really
doesn't matter what he call
>> you know at the end of the day and just
having that mentality and you got to
practice like that each and every day
out and ultimately you take that to
Sundays so that's just who I am and
ultimately I know, you know, with that
attitude, with that mindset and, you
know, that's how you play in this league
a long time. So, that's that's that's
what I'm about.
>> When you um you know, you look at at at
the the sacks you put up last year, a
little bit of a late bloomer in terms of
the sack production in your career,
doubters might say you might be a
one-year wonder. You might think, well,
this is a sign of things to come. How do
you kind of ensure that that this is a
sign of things to come that your game is
is going to the next level in terms of
being a pass rusher?
>> Well, the do the doubters is not
watching film, you know. I played in
schemes where though, you know, that was
that was a lot of movement up front, you
know. Um, and then I played in schemes a
scheme where though, you know, I'm able
to be on the edge and I'm able to rush
relentlessly and I'm able to let it rip.
And ultimately, you know, hey, when you
get an opportunity to play free, you go
out there and you do what you do best.
But sometimes, you know, there's some
systems where the call dictate certain
things, you know, what you doing, how
you moving, and um, you know, again, and
then also you got coaches, you got
teammates you playing with. There's a
lot that factors to it. And also being
healthy and also, you know, holding
yourself accountable to to to get it
done. So, I mean, it's just
I'm I don't really care about the
doubters. It doesn't bother me. Only
thing it do is just few add more fuel to
um you know, what I know I'mma do, you
know. Absolutely. I love it. You know, I
I love, you know, the doubters and stuff
like that. And actually, if they could
write a little bit more and say a little
bit more, you know, that that would help
as well. You know, that that would
absolutely give me that fuel, you know,
to the fire. And um you know, that's how
you remove the doubts. And either you
have a good season or whatever. You have
11 sacks 13, 14, 15. There's also always
people optimistic and they're going to
say this, they're going to say that.
Doesn't really matter, you know, at the
end of the day. Ultimately, what matters
is is, you know, um you doing the little
things day in and day out and ultimately
control the controllables, you know, and
absolut and then you you you are what
you repeatedly do. So that's kind of my
motto, my mindset. And then um you know
the doubters they they're the reason why
you know um guys like myself
um have the edge that he that that he
has that I have. So it's I love it. It's
amazing. It's it's a beautiful thing.
>> We'll go to Greg Almond. If any media
have questions, please raise your hand.
>> Hey, you were talking about just putting
the time in there in Detroit and
obviously had a breakout year last year.
How much did Detroit try and keep you
and what all went into the decision not
to return but to get a fresh start here
in Tampa?
>> Um, you know, I don't really know um
Detroit, you know, how they thought
about it or exactly what went into it,
but um and
I don't really care. I'm in Tampa and
I'm happy to be in Tampa,
>> you know, and um if I'm not mistaken,
they're on a schedule this year.
>> So, you know, um I'm excited about that.
Um
and uh you know, I I do love Detroit and
it was amazing. It was amazing. is a
great organization and I appreciate them
for giving me the opportunity to go out
there and uh do some great things and um
I look forward to also playing against
them.
>> Hey, one more. Just tell us real quick,
how do you pronounce your first name so
we know we have it right?
>> It's Aluadin.
>> Aquadine. Thank you, man.
>> Yeah,
>> we'll go to Scott Reynolds.
Aquadine, you went up against one of the
best offensive tackles in the game on a
regular basis in practice and pane so
well. The Bucks have got two really good
ones too in Tristan Worfs and Luke Geti.
How much are you looking forward to kind
of that iron sharpens iron mentality in
training camp and going up against you
know two of the best tackles and what
are your thoughts on on gettaki and
warps?
the the the best thing about um you know
in house having two great tackles is
that again we talk ball you know it
ain't personal we're trying to get each
other you know better and stuff like
that so it's actually um it's it's I
wouldn't have it I wouldn't want it any
other way you know because um you know
ultimately that what that's going to
help me that's gonna help the team
that's gonna help all of us the whole
organization you know on Sundays So, uh,
I look forward to, you know, sharpening
our skills together and, um, you know,
actually getting to work and grinding,
you know, with those guys, with that
crew.
>> And what are your thoughts on Yaya Diab?
He led the Bucks in sacks last year. I
think had a sack on Jared Goff on the
the Monday night game, but what do you
know about him and and his game? I think
Yaya um he's going to have a great year
and um to be honest um
I can't wait to work with him. I can't
work to see how he view ball and how he
see things and you know some of the
things he like to do as far as a pass
rush and ultimately I'm going to help
him in every way I can. And you never
know you know I could learn some things
from him as well. you know, it doesn't
matter younger, older. You know, it may
be some things that uh, you know, he do
that I don't exactly do or I don't see
it the same way he see it, but
ultimately, you know, um, I'mma give him
everything, you know, I I got as far as
the way I play and then, um, some of the
things I like to do and how I view pass
rush and and we going to work together.
We going to start that from day one, you
know. we going to work together and um
we going to we going to do some amazing
thing, you know. Um and he has a bright
future, super talented, you know, and
it's it's little things that I've
already seen on film that I would love
to I can't wait to share with him, you
know, that's going to help all of us get
better, you know, and and that's what we
going to do. We're gonna work together
and uh we gonna start this thing from
ground. We're gonna start it from ground
up, you know, and I'm I'm I'm extremely
excited and it's it's going to be fun.
It's going to be extremely fun.
>> Thank you. Welcome to Tampa.
>> Thank you.
>> All right, that's all we have.
Appreciate you guys joining us.